NARRATOR: Kids,the secret to dating is very simple:
孩儿们 约会的秘诀其实很简单
confident,be comfortable in your skin, be assured of who you are.
信心满满 泰然自若 相信自我
Uncle Barney was really good at that last one,
Barney叔叔对最后一点游刃有余
even though a lot of the time who he was was someone else.
尽管很多时候他并非本色出演
Hi.Do you see that guy over there in the scuba suit?
嗨 看见那边穿潜水衣的家伙了吗?
You inking of going and talking to him?
你想上去和他搭讪?
No.Good.
- 不想 - 很好
He's seriously the biggest jerk on the face of the Earth.
他是举世无双的超级大混球
How do you know him?
你咋知道?
Oh,he's one of my best friends.
他是我死党
So what's with the scuba suit?
那潜水衣是咋回事?
Well,it's a long story.
说来话长
See,he just went through a breakup...
他刚失恋不久
NARRATOR: There's two basic philosophies of how to handle yourself after a breakup.
失恋后一般会有两种处世之道
- Some people throw themselves into... - My career.
- 有的人全身心投入... - 我的事业
That's my number one focus right now.
现在我以事业为重
From now on,nmore dating.
从现在起 不涉红尘
It's all about work.
事业至上
NARRATOR: While others throw themselves into...
而有的人则是投身于...
Every woman in New York City.
整座纽约市的姑娘们
That's right,Barney Stinson is back on the market.
没错 Barnry Stinson卷土重来了
Mothers,lock up your daughters.Daughters,lock up your MILSWANCAs.
妈妈要看紧自家女儿 女儿要看紧自家的MILSWANCA
- MILSWANCAs? - Wait,I can get this.
- MILSWANCA - 等等 我明白啦
Mothers I'd Like To Sleep With And Never Call Again.
我一睡完就决不联系的妈妈们
Correct!Cile gets the square.
正确! 太阳打西边出来了
Don't you think you're kinda rushg back into this?
你不觉得这样太快了点吗?
Lily,since I started dating Robin,there's a certain thing I haven't used as much as I would like .
Lily 我和Robin约会开始 有样东西 尽管我心痒痒 但还是没拿出来用 (Lily姐想歪了)
It's...kinda big, surprisingly heavy, kind of leathery, and it's black.
它有点大 绝对重量级 皮质的 而且是黑色的
This,my friends...
就是这个 朋友们...
is The Playbook.
游龙戏凤秘籍
The Playbook contains every scam,con,hustle, hoodwink,gambit,flimflam,
游龙戏凤秘籍包含了所有 亲身实践过的或者跃跃欲试的
stratagem and bamboozle I've ever used-- or ever hope to use--
计谋 骗局 圈套 障眼法 诡计 诈术 谋略和骗术
to pick up chicks and give them the business.
用来泡妞爽翻天
Wow,you wrote another book?
哇 你还写了别的书啊?
we got a...
真是...
Stephen King over here.
堪比Stephen King啊(美国多产作家)
It's all in here.
都在这了
Everything from basic moves like "The Don't Drink That.
从最基本的象"表喝"开始
" Whoa,don't drink that.I saw some guy slip something in there.
"哇 表喝 我看见有人往里放了东西"
What?Who?
什么? 谁?
that guy.
那家伙
Thank you.
谢谢
To more advanced maneuvers like "ThMrs.Stinsfire.
到更高级的计谋象"Stinfire太太"
" Now Kappas,after our disciplinary hearing for lewd behavr last semester,
上学期对于行为不端的惩戒听证会之后
we have been aigned a new housemom.
我们聘请了新的管家
I'd like you to meet Mrs.Stinsfire.
大家来见见Stinsfire太太吧
Hello,girls!
你们好 姑娘们!
I can't picture a way that wouldn't work.
真是想失败都难
What's "The Loreo Von Matterhorn"?
"Lorenzo Von Matterhorn"是啥?
I'm glad you asked.
问得好
"The Lorenzo Von Matterhorn" will be my grand return to the sge.
"Lorenzo Von Matterhorn" 将是我重出江湖的舞台
Or y know,the bed.
换句话说就是我的床
Actually,my bed isind of on a stage.
其实 我的床就是个舞台
I put a platform underneath, and got some lights going.It's a real production.
我在床下摆了台阶 还装了聚光灯 绝对是实打实的
Barney exits!
Barney闪啦!
So,how about you, Robin?You getting back out there?ere is your playbook?
你咋样 Robin? 你又是单身贵族了 你的游龙戏凤秘籍呢?
My playbook?Bro,uh,two-volume set,right here.
我的游龙戏凤秘籍 有两卷呢 就在这
It's a great read actually.
读起来可真带劲
Yeah,I'm reading it right now.
嗯 我正读着呢
Anyway,I told you already,I'm taking a break from all that.
我说过了 我要缓一段时间
Marshall, it's totally gonna happen.
Marshall 绝对会发生
- So gna happen. - What's gonna happen?
- 是啊 - 发生什么?
- You're gonna fl in love. - So soon.
- 你会坠入爱河 - 很快
Not likel I'm focusing on my career.I'm done with dating.
不可能 我现在以事业为重 不问红尘了
Oh,okay,we playing The Pymid?
好吧 想玩金字塔对吧?
Okay,uh, "Things people say right before they meet thlove of their life.
好吧 "遇到真爱前的大言不惭"
Kelly Harris, girl I went to law school with said...
Kelly Harris 和我一起上法学院的姑娘说
: Hey,law school'so hard, I just want to focus on my studies.
嘿 法学好难读 我要一门心思读书
Six months later?
6个月后?
Married!
结婚啦!
- We,that's all well and good... - Travis Frenchroy,backup bartender tells me...
- 那也不错 - Travis Frenchroy 候补酒保告诉我...
: Oh,I'm so over the whole dating ga.
我不想再约会了
I just want to focus on my Star Trek fan fiction.
我只想看我的"星际迷航"
Six months later...
6个月后...
Married!
结婚啦!
May I respond?
我能说句吗?
Well,that's all well and good for them...
对他们来说这样也好
Matthew Blitz, accountant at my office says...:
Matthew Blitz 我办公室的会计说
Oh,I'm gonna die single and alone.
我要孤独终老
I might as well just focus on this year's taxes.
我还是把心思放在今年的税上吧
Six months later?
6个月后?
民事结合并打算结婚 正等着 纽约州参议院通过同性恋婚姻法
Protest all you want, t it's gonna happen.
尽管你不想 但还是会发生
- It's a law of nature. - Lawyered.Of nature.
- 这是自然法则 - 自然而然的事
Believe me,I'd love to have no interest in a relationship.
相信我 要是我不想谈恋爱就好了
There's no way I'd be single right now if I wanted to be single.
要是我一心想着单身 就不会到现在仍单身
Okay,now you're ready.
好吧 你终于准备好了
Ready for what?
准备好啥?
Three years ago, this girl Shelly started teaching at my school.
3年前 有个叫Shelly的姑娘 在我的学校任职
The moment I saw her,I was like, "This is the gi for Ted.
我一看见她 就感觉"和Ted真是天生一对"
" Why am I just hearing abt her now?
为啥你现在才对我说?
3年前
You ow,I usually hate being set up but this Ted jt sounds so great.
我一直对相亲很反感 但这个Ted听上去不错
Oh,he is.He's so sweet and thoughtful and intelligent.
是啊 他人很好  聪明又贴心
MARSHALL: Come o buddy!One more chicken finger and the crown is yours!
来吧 哥们! 再塞跟鸡条我们就赢啦!
Hmm,I don't see him anywhere.He must be out doing charity work.
我没看见他 他肯定出去做社工了
So,different bar?
换家酒吧咋样?
: That gi with Lily's pretty cute!
和Lily一起的姑娘真可爱!
Oh,yeahshe was cute.
嗯 她真可爱
Yeah,still is.And now you're ready.
嗯 仍不减当年 现在你准备就绪了
Yeah,bro,now yocan fit like, three times as many chicken fingers in your mouth.
嗯 哥们 现在你都能塞下3倍的鸡条啦
You know it.
说得对
Okay,I will set it up, but promise me you won't do anything stupid.
好吧 我来安排 但要保证不会再干蠢事
I promise I won'do anything stupid.
保证不干蠢事
And I kept that promise.But only because...
我说到做到了 只因...
she never showed up.
她没出现
I know.I'm sorry, I feel terrible.
我知道 抱歉 我感觉挺糟的
You should feel teible!
你应该觉得挺糟的!
I do feel terrible!I do!
我真觉得糟透了! 真的!
- You should!You should!You should! - I do,I do!
- 你应该的! 应该的! 应该的! - 真的 真的!
I don't.
假的
Look,I was really loing forward to meeting Ted,
听着 我真的很期待和Ted见面
but I got to the bar an hour early and I met this amazing guy.
但我提前一小时到酒吧时 遇见了超牛的人
ke,seriously amazing.
真的超牛
And you met him at MacLaren's?
你在麦克拉伦酒吧里遇到的?
- Yeah,right at the bar. - What's h name?
- 对 就在那 - 他叫什么名字?
I shouldn't say.
我不该说
Oh,what the heck.It's Lorenzo Von Matterhorn!
管他呢 是Lorenzo Von Matterhorn!
你这个挨千刀的!
So,he hooked up with Shelly?You must've been pisd.
他泡了Shelly? 你肯定气坏了
Damn straight.
这还用问
BarneyI've had Shelly set aside for Ted for three years.
Barney 为了Ted  我把Shelly雪藏了3年
Dude,Ted was not missing out.
姐们 Ted没错过啥啊
She's brainy and annoying, kind of boring in the sack.
她很聪明又很烦人 到了床上又象死鱼一条
Oh,I guess she would've been perfect for Ted.
她的确和Ted是绝配
Had I known that she was the to meet Ted, of course I wouldn have done it,but...
要是我知道是去见Ted的 当然我不会下手
given the circumstances, I thk Ted'll be proud of me.
但鉴于这种情况 我觉得Ted会为我感到骄傲
I pulled off "ThLorenzo Von Matterhorn.
"Lorenzo Von Matterhorn"计谋成功啦
" Okay,what's the Lorenzo Von Matterhorn?
好吧 Lorenzo Von Matterhorn到底是啥?
My question exactly.
我也这么问的
Okay,what's the Lorenzo Von Matterhorn?
好吧 Lorenzo Von Matterhorn是什么?
Glad you asked.
问得好
the Lorenzo Von Matterhorn
Lorenzo Von Matterhorn
BARNEY: To perform the Lorenzo Von Matterhorn, here's what you'll need:
就是假装是Lorenzo Von Matterhorn
Basic knowledge of Web site design and a very unique fake ne.
只要会基本的网页设计和一个独一无二的假名字
So,think of your fake namright now.
想想取啥名字吧
Have you g it?Good.
想到了? 很好
Now,select your target.
现在 选择目标
Preferably a girl with a real ni...phone.
最好是拿着华丽丽手机的妞
Yeah,it's me.
没错 就是我
Do I know you?
我认识你吗?
I'm Lorenzo Von Matterhorn.
我是Lorenzo Von Matterhorn
Are you,like, famous or something?
你是名人还是咋的?
Yes.
对
你真不知道我是谁 对吧?
What a refreshing change opace.ce to meet you...
真是不可思议 遇见你很高兴
Shelly.
Shelly
Once again, I'm Lorenzo Von Matterhorn.
再说一遍 我是Lorenzo Von Matterhorn
Spelled like it sounds two "T"s.
正如其发音一样 有两个T
Lorenzo Von Matterhorn.
Lorenzo Von Matterhorn
Ciao.
再见
BARNEY: Then,as soon as you're gone, she gets out her phone
只要你一走 她就掏出手机
and does an Internet searc for Lorenzo Von Matterhorn.
开始上网查Lorenzo Von Matterhorn
And that's whenshe discovers.
这就是她查到的
a series of fake Web sites, all devoted to the incredible life of Lorenzo Von Matterhorn.
一连串描述Lorenzo Von Matterhorn 传奇人生的虚假网页
There's the fake business article about Lorenzo, the reclusive billionaire.
介绍Lorenzo的商业撰文 身价亿万的隐士
The fake Explorers Club newsletter describing his balloon trek to the North Pole
探险俱乐部关于他乘热气球 只身前往北极的简报
as a feat of pure daring and imagination.
实乃大胆而富有创造力的壮举
The fake medical journal featuring the heartbreaking story of doctors
以及医生悲痛欲绝地劝导其别做阴茎缩短术
telling him penis reduction surgery isn't an option.
为专栏特写的医药杂志
And by the time you get back.
这时你正好回来
Hi,Shelly, uh,I hate to be forward, but can I buy you a cup of coffee?
嗨 Shelly 我不喜欢进展太快 但我能请你喝咖啡吗?
Yes!Please.
好! 拜托
What does ffee go for these days,$50?
最近咖啡多少钱 50块?
: Oh,Lorenzo.
噢 Lorenzo
And it is on.
好戏开~场
That's awful.
真卑鄙
You alize you broke her heart,right?
你明知道伤她心了 对吧?
She's inconsolable.
她伤心欲绝
Why would shbe inconsolable?
她为何会伤心欲绝?
Lorenzo's balloon won't sappear over the Arctic for another week.
Lorenzo的热气球下周 就在北极上空消失了
The only way she would be upset is if someone told her it waall a bunch of lies.
除非有人告诉这一切全是谎言 她才会伤心欲绝
Itas all just a bunch of lies?
这一切全是谎言?
It was all just a bunch of lies.
全是谎言
- The balloon expedition? - Lies!
- 热气球探险? - 骗人的!
- The man-made island shaped like his face off the coast of Dubai? - Lies!
- 迪拜海岸边上照着他的脸型而造的人工岛 - 骗人的!
Finishing third in the laser tag competition?
激光枪比赛排名第三?
Li-- Oh,actually, that one's true.I went to that.
骗... 那倒是真的 我也去了
- You went to the Vatican? - Lies!
- 你去梵蒂冈了? - 骗人的!
Oh,my God!
我的天!
Well,I hope you're happy with yourself.
你现在满意了
- What? - You broke that girl's heart.
- 什么啊? - 你碾碎了那姑娘的心
- Me? - You!
- 我? - 你!
She'll probably never trust a guy again.
她可能不会再相信别人了
You ruined her for Ted.
为了Ted 你毁了她
Noto mention Julio Von Matterhorn, Lorenzo's twin brother.
更别说Julio Von Matterhorn Lorenzo的孪生弟弟了
Can you believe that?He blames me
难以置信 他竟然怪到我头上
Oh,and by the way,Ted, I bet she'd still go out with you.
还有 Ted 我想她还会和你约会的
m,let me think.Do I want to go out with a girl Barney hooked up with?
我想想 我想和Barney泡过的妞约会吗?
Guys,help me out with the harmonies.Sure.
- 伙计们 帮我来段和声 - 行
* Hell no...
不可能...
Well,you st be a little bothered by this.
你还为这些感到不快吗?
Well,it's his life.Look,if these girls are dumb enough to fall for this crap,
那是他的人生 听着 要是那些 姑娘聪明点就不会上当
Agreed.Have you seen the one there labeled "The SNASA"?
同意 你看到那个"SNASA"了吗?
"The SNASA"
"SNASA"
Wow,you're an astronaut?
哇 你是宇航员?
I'm actually in a top secret governnt space program called Secret NASA or SNASA.
其实我在做一个绝密的政府太空项目 叫绝密NASA或者秘之NASA
Wow,SNASA.
挖无 秘之总署
Do you go to the Moon and stuff?
你去过月球还是啥的吗?
Well,not the Moon you're familiar with, though I have been to the Smoon.
算是去过 不过不是你平时见到的月球 叫秘之月
Wow,t Smoon.
挖无 秘之月
Ifou fall for that one, my heart breaks for you, but I'm sorry, you're a smoron.
要是你连这都信 我真为你伤心 得罪说一句 你是个秘之蠢材
So,what hapns next?
然后呢?
Come on,Barney, you just...
别这样 Barney 你刚...
You just got out oan honest to God relationship.
你刚从一段神圣的爱情中恢复单身
You're a real boy now.
你现在已经成长为男子汉了
You can't go back to these cheap tricks.
不能再用以前那些低俗伎俩
Cheap tricks?
低俗伎俩?
Not one of these is a cheap trick.
这些方法没有一个是低俗伎俩
Except for "The Cheap Trick.
除了"低俗伎俩"
" I'm the bass playerfor Cheap Trick.
我是低俗伎俩乐队的贝斯手
And even that one involves expensive hair extensions.
就算是这个  那套假发也还是高级货
Now,if you don't mind, I am off to prepare for toght's main event.
好了 不介意的话  我要开始今晚的活动
I will be performing "The 's Not Coming.
我要去实施"他不会来了"
" Glad you asked.
问得好
The 's Not Coming.
"他不会来了"
BARNEY: To perform "The He's Not Coming," here's what you'll need:
要实施"他不会来了"  你需要:
The observation deck of the Empire Ste Building.
帝国大厦的观赏层
Are you there?
上去了吗?
Good.
很好
For generations, this has been the spot New Yorkers have chosen
这里一直以来都被纽约客选为
for their romantic reunions with long-estranged lovers,
长期未见的情侣浪漫重逢之地
so all you have to do is walk up to every girl you see and say...
你只需要跟每个你见到的女生说...
他不会来了
What are you talking about?
你在说什么?
Never mind.
请无视我
He's not coming.
他不会来了
She's not coming?Sorry.
她不会来了? 不好意思
Until sooner or later...
迟早...
He's not coming.
他不会来了
He's not?
他不来了?
But we agreed.
可我们说好了
We always said we'd meet here.
我们要在这里见面的
On this night.
就在今晚
: I'm such a fool.
我真是个傻瓜
All right,I'm going to go get the paper.
我去拿报纸
More like, go get a husband.
是去捡个老公吧
- Totally. - Okay,you guys need to stop at,seriously.
- 说得好 - 说真的 你们别再这样了
The last thing I am looking for right now is a relationship.
我现在对恋爱完全没兴趣
When you pick up that newspaper, be sure to check the wedding announcements.
去拿报纸的时候  记得看看结婚通告
: For yours.
是你的哟
MARSLL: Robin,it's like this.
Robin 是这样的
Do you have anidea how many times in my life I've gone to t freezer
你知道我这辈子有多少次打开冰箱
looking for frozen waffles and not found them?
想找些冰华夫饼而没找着?
- Thousands? - Millions.
- 上千次? - 上百万次
But when I go to the freezer loing for a Popsicle--
但当我打开冰箱想找些冰棒
or the remote control because Lily and I are having a fight and she's hidden it there--
或者遥控器 因为我和Lily一吵架  她就会把它藏那儿
you know what I fi?Frozen waffles.
知道我找到什么了吗? 冰华夫饼
That's how it works.You go out there looking for a paper,
就是这样 你出去拿报纸
you're coming back with frozen waffles.
你一回来后头就会跟着个冰华夫饼
And,in this case,frozen waffles
我说的这个冰华夫饼 是个男人
Also,could you pick up some frozen waffles?
对了 能帮我带点冰华夫饼回来吗?
In that case,frozen waffles...
这次我说的冰华夫饼...
are frozen waffles.
就是冰华夫饼
Guys,code red!Emergency.Lockdown.
红色警报! 紧急情况 一级防守
- Nobody's leaving. - Whoa,what happened?
- 大家都别走 - 怎么了?
I tried "The He's Not Coming," anit worked.Gangbusters.
我用了"他不会来了"这招 大成功 搞定
Yoshould have seen this girl.
你得见见这妞
Bang,ping, pa-dowga-donk.
美得没话说哦!
Okay,I'm leaving.
好了 我走了
So,we get up to my place, and I go intmy room to set up the camera--
然后我们去我家  当我先行一步设好摄像机 (冠西哥!?)
to light the candles-- and when I come out, she's gone,
先行一步点好蜡烛... 回来一看 她不见了
and so is The Playok!
游龙戏凤秘籍也不见了!
I think we all know who is responsible for this.
我想大家都知道是谁干的好事
Yeah,we do.
地球人都知道
Al-Qaeda.
"基地"组织
No,you idiot.
才不是呢 笨死了
It was me.
是我干的
你~这狗娘养的!
Wow,you stole The Playbook?
挖无 你偷了游龙戏凤秘籍?
So,the girl on the Empire State Building?
帝国大厦那个女生是?
A iend of mine-- an actress.
我的朋友... 是演员
An actress.Of course.
演员 怪不得
That explains her impeccable diction and her sluttiness.
怪不得她发音字正腔圆 性格淫荡
Barney 我要把那本游龙戏凤秘籍
and put it up on thenternet for the whole world to see.
放上网让全世界的人看到
You wouldn't.
千万不要
I won't,as long as you agree to no more scams,no morcons,
我不会的 只要你保证不再用计谋 骗局 圈套
no more hustles, no more hoodwinks, no more gambits, no more stratagems and no more bamboozles.
不再用障眼法 诡计 以后没有诈术 谋略
- I notice you left out flimflams. - No more flimflams!
- 你漏掉了 满嘴跑火车 - 不再满嘴跑火车!
Damn it.
可恶
Oh,my God.I-I'm rry to interrupt, but look at this.
买糕的 不好意思打断一下 你们看
No.
不是吧
"Ted Mosby"
I got left at the altar.
我在婚礼前被甩了 (学习Ted啊)
Oh,my God,that's horrible.
太恶劣了
I wonder if that would work.
不知道有没有效呢?
That's not even the worst one in here.
那还不是最恶劣的
Have you guys se,uh, "My Penis Grants Wishes"?
你们有看过那 "我是鸡鸡神灯"吗?
Really?A genie comes t of it?
真的? 会有个神仙冒出来?
Only if yorub it hard enough.
要大力点擦才会有哦
So,then,what happened?
那然后呢?
It says here he brea into song, and then the furniture comes to life and dances with him.
这里写着 他突然唱起歌来 然后家具都活过来与他共舞
It's not very well thought out.
仔细想想还是不够好
It's no "Mrs.Stinsfire.
不如 "Stinfire夫人"好
" No,what happened in real life?
我是说现实生活之后怎样了?
Well,a few hours later...
几个小时之后...
You know, I heard it was gonna rain.
呃 我听说今天要下雨
Ifnyone's interested, I will be at MacLaren's Pub
如果你们有兴趣 我会在MacLaren's酒吧
performing a pla out of The Playbookentitled
再现一场游龙戏凤秘籍中伎俩 名曰
"The S That is all.
"潜水员" 完毕
Okay,that's it.I'm putting The Playbook up on the Internet.
够了 我要把游龙戏凤秘籍放上网
Baby,can you put The Playbook up on the Internet?
宝贝 帮我把游龙戏凤秘籍放上网好吗?
Of course,baby, but here's the...here's the weird thing.
好的 但是...奇怪的是
I have literally been through this book cover to cover.
我已经看过这书很多遍了
There is no play in here called "The Scuba Diver.
这里没有记载什么"潜水员"呀
So,w you guys want to know what "The Scuba Diver" is.
现在你们想知道 "潜水员"是什么了
Well,it was on the last page of The Playbook, but I ripped it out just in case.
那是在游龙戏凤秘籍最后一页  不过我把它撕下来了 以防万一
777 You're about to see it in action.
别担心 你们将会见到我的现场表演
See the blond over there by the bar?
见到那边的金发女郎了吗?
Tizzarget acquizzired.
目~标 锁~定
Barney,don't do this.
Barney 别这样
- You're so... - Ah,give it a rest,pest.
- 你真的很... - 歇歇吧 害人精
If anyone should be mad, it should be Rob.
要生气也该是Robin生气
She loves The Playbook.
她可爱游龙戏凤秘籍了
I don't love The Playbook.
我不爱游龙戏凤秘籍
What are you talk...
你说什...
The Playbook-- it's ld.You got to admit it's pretty spectacular.
是游龙戏凤秘籍 这么酷 你得承认 它无与伦比吧
Look,Barney,we just broke up.
Barney 我们刚分手
I mean,yes, the costumes are cute,but...
没错 这身装束确实很可爱 可...
we just broke up.
我们刚分手呀 (快复合快复合!)
Well,I didn't...I didn't know you felt that way.
我... 我没想到你会这么想
I guess I've been so wrapped up in my own stuff that I...
可能是我太专注于自己所以...
Oh,crap, she's looking over he.Quick,everyone, scatter.
要糟 她看过来了  所有人 给我散
That's it.
够了
You see at guy over there in the scuba suit?
嗨 见到那边穿潜水服的家伙了吗?
And that brings us to rig now.
事情就是这样
But...wait.So,why is he wearing scuba gear?
可是...等等  到底为啥他穿着潜水服?
We don't know.
不知道
And it's killing us, Claire.
我们都好奇死了 Claire
It's killing us!
好奇死了!
Let's go ask him.
那问问他呀
So,what's "The Scuba Diver"?
"潜水员"是什么?
And this iClaire,by the way.
顺便 这是Claire
Hello,Claire.Myame is Lieutenant Frank Lyman.
你好 Claire 我叫Frank Lyman中尉
I train bomb sniffing dolphi for the Balt...
专门为波罗的海边居民 训练炸弹侦查海豚...
You know what?
知道吗?
I'm...I can't...I can't...I can't do ts.
我...我做不下去了
Robin...I so sorry.
Robin...对不起
I guess this breakup's been touer on me than I thought.
这次分手比我想象中更痛苦
I think this playbook was just a way to takemy mind
游龙戏凤秘籍只是让我逃避现实而已
It's okay.It's been tough on me,too.
没事 我也很痛苦
I mean,look at me.I've sworn off relationships.
你看 我都赌誓不再恋爱了
- She's so about to get married.I got to make sure my tux fits. - I got to work on my toast.
- 她肯定得结婚 我得整整我那礼服 - 我得想想祝酒词了
I will bang your heads together like coconuts.
信不信我把你们俩的脑壳当椰子一样锤
LILY: Barney,I'm so glad you're stopping this.
Barney 你不再任性我太欣慰了
And-and,frankly, the real Barney is way cooler than any of the fake Barneys in this aybook.
还有 说真的 真正的Barney比 这书上说的假Barney酷多了
Oh,is that right?
真的吗?
Claire,you've prably heard a lot about the real Barney tonight.
Claire 今晚你可能听过 太多真正Barney的故事
Want to grab a cup of coffee?
想去喝杯咖啡吗?
Claire,before you turn him down, I-I think you should know that under this neoprene suit
Claire 在你拒绝他之前  我得说 在这身橡胶衣底下
with what appears to be a tube sock stuffed in the crotch.
虽然裤裆穿着类似于圆筒长袜的东西
Can of Pringles, but go on.
品客薯片的罐子 不过继续
is an amazing guy.
是个好男人
He's fun and one of my best friends.
他很风趣 是我最好的朋友之一
And he landed this hottie.
而且他把过这辣妹哦
He's a good guy.
他是个好男人
Come on,Claire, go out with him.
Claire 跟他出去吧
MARSHALL: It's just a cup of coffee,right?
只不过是一杯咖啡
- Right?Come on. - LILY: Can't hurt.
- 去吧 - 没事的
All right,all right.Let's t some coffee.
好吧好吧 我们去喝杯咖啡吧
NARRATOR: And by the end of the night...
那晚最后...
I'm prd of that guy.
真为他自豪
To be that vulnerable takes a lot of Prings.
要装成那样可得费不少品客
I got a text from Barney.
Barney的短信
"Look under the table.
"看看桌子底下"
- It's a page from The Playbook. - What does it say?
- 是游龙戏凤秘籍的一页 - 写了什么?
's "The Scuba Diver.
是"潜水员"
" BARNEY: Step one: tell a meddlesome female friend about The Playbook.
第一步 告诉你爱管闲事的女性朋友 关于游龙戏凤秘籍的事
Step two: run play on one of her coworkers, king her so angry ****
第二步 在她的同事身上用一招 使其生气并偷走游龙戏凤秘籍
*** and tell her you're gog to do one more scam
第三步 穿上潜水服  告诉她你要再设一次局
called "The Scuba Diver" on the hot girl standing by the bar.
叫"潜水员" 骗倒酒吧里的美女
Your fend-- let's call her Lily-- goes and talks to the girl
你的朋友 就叫她Lily吧  会跟那女孩搭讪
and tells her everything about The Playbook.
并告诉她游龙戏凤秘籍的一切
Now,here's where it gets tricky.
接着就是这招的精妙之处
When Lily and the girl ask at "The Scuba Diver" is, *****
当那女孩和Lily问起"潜水员"是什么 脱下潜水镜
about your deep-seated insecurities which don't really exist
说些捏造的掏心窝的话
because-- let's face it-- you're awesome.
因为 承认吧 你棒极了
Feeling bad for you, Lily talks you up tohe girl,who then agrees to go get coffee with you.
出于同情 Lily会说服女孩与你共进咖啡
And it...is...on.
然后 好戏上...场
你~这狗娘养的
I'll give you a call.Bye-bye.
再打给你哦 拜拜
Uh,for those of you keeping score, "The Ted Mosby" works.
你们给我记住了 "Ted Mosby"这招 大成功哦
Robin,here we go.
Robin 来了
你说你不想拍拖
Well,the love of your life is about to walk through the door, and it's...
你的真命天子将会走进门 就是...
thatuy.
他
Yeah,I'm not falling in love withhat guy.
呃 我不会跟他拍拖的
Right,right,right, because it's going to be...
当然 当然 因为那会是...
th guy.
他
Mmm,I don't know.The blue blazer's just, like,not doing it for me,so...
嗯 蓝色上衣 不太吸引我呢
Yeah,yeah.You're right,'cause here he comes.It's that guy!
没错 没错 因为那人是他!
Oh,Robin.
噢 Robin
You should at least give her a chance.You know,make out with h a little, see if there's sothing there.
你得给个机会她 跟她亲热一下  看看有没有火花什么的
- Okay,I'm going to work. - Yeah,you are.
- 好 我要去干活了 - 加油哦
No,m actually going to work.
不 我真的要去干活
- Go,work it. - NARRATOR: And the ironic part was...
- 去吧 好好干 - 讽刺的是...
Are you Robin?
Robin是吗?
Don,your new cohost.
Don 新的主持人
那天她遇见了Don
Damn it,Marshall.
可恶 Marshall